Guide to the Arthur A. Allen papers,1899-1968,
Allen, Arthur A. papers,1899-1968,
- Series I. Biographical Materials
  - Business Correspondence
    - E-G, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - H-K, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - L-M, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - N-P, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - R-S, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - T-Z, 1948 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - January -July 1, 1949: A-E, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - January -July 1, 1949: F-L, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - January -July 1, 1949: M-P, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - January -July 1, 1949: R-Z, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - July-December 1949: A-D, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - July-December 1949: E-M, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - July-December 1949: N-Z, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - January - April 1, 1949: A-J, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - January - April 1, 1949: K-Z, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - April - July 1, 1950: A-H, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - April - July 1, 1950: I-Z, 1950 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - July 1950-January 1, 1951: A-K, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - July 1950-January 1, 1951: L-z, 1950-1951 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - January - April 1951: A-H, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - January - April 1951: I-Z, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - April - July 1, 1951: A-I, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - April - July 1, 1951: J-Z, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - July 1951 - October 1951: A-I, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - July 1951 - October 1951: J-Z, 1951 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - October 1951 - January 1952: A-J, 1951-1952 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - October 1951 - January 1952: K-Z, 1951-1952 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - January - February 1952: A-G, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - January - February 1952: H-P, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - January - February 1952: Q-Z, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - March - April 1952: A-C, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - March - April 1952: D-G, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - March - April 1952: H-O, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - March - April 1952: P-Z, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - May - June 1952: A-F, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - May - June 1952: G-L, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - May - June 1952: M-Q, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - May - June 1952: R-Z, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - July - August 1952: A-F, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - July - August 1952: G-O, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - July - August 1952: P-Z, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - September - October: A-I, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - September - October: J-Z, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - November - December: A-J, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - November - December: K-Z, 1952 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - January - February 1953: A-E, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - January - February 1953: F-M, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - January - February 1953: N-Z, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - March - April 1953: A-E, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - March - April 1953: F-K, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - March - April 1953: M-R, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - March - April 1953: S-Z, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - May - June 1953: A-L, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - May - June 1953: M-Z, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - July - August 1953: A-Z, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - September - October 1953: A-L, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - September - October 1953: M-Z, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - November - December 1953 A-K, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - November - December 1953 L-Z, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - January - February 1954: A-K, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - January - February 1954: L-Z, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - March - April 1954: A-H, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - March - April 1954: I-S, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - March - April 1954: T-Z, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - May - June 1954: A-F, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - May - June 1954: G-N, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - May - June 1954: O-Z, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - July - August 1954: A-Z, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - September - October 1954: A-Z, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - November - December 1954: A-L, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - November - December 1954: M-Z, 1954 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - January - February 1955: A-E, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - January - February 1955: F-O, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - January - February 1955: P-Z, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - March - April 1955: A-D, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - March - April 1955: E-K, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - March - April 1955: L-Z, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - April - June 1955: A-J, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - May-June 1955: J-Z, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - July - October 1955: A-G, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - July - October 1955: H-Z, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - November - December 1955: A-K, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - November - December 1955: L-Z, 1955 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - January - March 1956: A-G, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - January - March 1956: H-L, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - January - March 1956: M-Z, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - April - June 1956: A-E, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - April - June 1956 (January 1957): F-M, 1956, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - April - June 1956: N-Z, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - July - October 1956: A-J, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - July - October 1956: K-O, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - July - October 1956: P-Z, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - November - December 1956: A-H, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - November - December 1956: I-Z, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - 1958-1960, 1958-1961 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - December 1956 - March 1957: A-G, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - December 1956 - March 1957: H-N, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - December 1956 - March 1957: O-Z, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - April - June 1957: A-M, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - April - June 1957: N-Z, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - July - November 1, 1957: A-K, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - July - November 1, 1957: L-Z, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - November - December 1957: A-Z, 1957 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - January - April 1958: A-L, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - January - April 1958: M-Z, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - May - September 1958: A-L, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - May - September 1958: M-Z, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - October - November 1958: A-Z, 1958 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Bird Slide Lists, c. 1954 and undated (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Bird Slide Lists/Catalogs, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - December 1958 - December 1959: A-E, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - December 1958 - December 1959: F-K, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - December 1958 - December 1959: L-P, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - December 1958 - December 1959: Q-Z, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - January - March 1960: A-L, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - January - March 1960: M-Z, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Bird Slide List/Catalog, 1958-1959 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - March - July 1960: A-H, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - March - July 1960: I-R, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - March - July 1960: S-Z, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Bird Slide List/Catalog, c. 1958 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - August - October 1960: A-D, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - August - October 1960: E-N, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - August - October 1960: O-Z, 1960 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Ward's of California, 1954-1964 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - General Biological Supply House, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - General Biological Supply House, 1959 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - General Biological Supply House, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - September - December 1960: A-P, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - October - December 1960: G-Z, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - January - March 1961: A-L, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - January - March 1961: M-Z, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - April - September 1961: A-F, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - April - September 1961: G-H, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - April - September 1961: I-Z, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - October - December1961: A-Z, 1961 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - January - June 1962: A-C, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - January - June 1962: D-H, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - January - June 1962: I-M, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - January - June 1962: N-Z, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - July - October 1962: A-D, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - July - October 1962: E-H, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - July - October 1962: I-R, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - July - October 1962: S-Z, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - November - December 1962: A-H, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - November - December 1962: J-Z, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - January - March 1963: A-D, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - January - March 1963: E-G, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - January - March 1963: H-L, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - January - March 1963: M-Z, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - April - August 1963: A-F, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - April - August 1963: G-M, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - April - August 1963: N-R, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - April - August 1963: S-Z, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - September - December 1963: A-F, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - September - December 1963: G-M, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - September - December 1963: N-Z, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Sally Hoyt, 1953-1959 (Box 181, Folder 1)
      Arthur's letters to Sally. Some of the items in this box have been treated for mold damage
    - Sally Hoyt, 1949-1967 (Box 181, Folder 2)
      Other materials relating to Sally Hoyt including letters, sketches and poems written by Sally Hoyt and Elsa Allen
      Some of the items in this box have been treated for mold damage
- Series II. Professional Correspondence
  - General - Alphabetical by Year
    - 1908-1911 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - 1912 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - 1913 (Box 28, Folder 3-7)
    - A-Z, 1914 (Box 28, Folder 8-13)
    - A-C, 1915 (Box 28, Folder 14-16)
    - D-Z, 1915 (Box 29, Folder 1-8)
    - A-Q, 1916 (Box 29, Folder 9-16)
    - R-Z, 1916 (Box 30, Folder 1-3)
    - A-Z, 1917 (Box 30, Folder 4-16)
    - A-Z, 1918 (Box 31, Folder 1-10)
    - A-E, 1919 (Box 31, Folder 11-14)
    - F-Z, 1919 (Box 32, Folder 1-9)
    - A-G, 1920 (Box 32, Folder 10-14)
    - H-Z, 1920 (Box 33, Folder 1-8)
    - A-K, 1921 (Box 33, Folder 9-15)
    - L-Z, 1921 (Box 34, Folder 1-7)
    - A-K, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 8-14)
    - L-Z, 1922 (Box 35, Folder 1-5)
    - A-F, 1923 (Box 35, Folder 6-14)
    - G-Z, 1923 (Box 36, Folder 1-14)
    - A, 1924 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - B-P, 1924 (Box 37, Folder 1-12)
    - R-Z, 1924 (Box 38, Folder 1-3)
    - A-L, 1925 (Box 38, Folder 4-14)
    - M-Z, 1925 (Box 39, Folder 1-5)
    - A-D, 1926 (Box 39, Folder 6-10)
    - E-S, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 1-10)
    - T-Z, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - A-K, 1927 (Box 41, Folder 3-12)
    - L-Z, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 1-8)
    - A-D, 1928 (Box 42, Folder 9-13)
    - E-R, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 1-12)
    - S-Z, 1928 (Box 44, Folder 1-3)
    - A-H, 1929 (Box 44, Folder 4-13)
    - I-Z, 1929 (Box 45, Folder 1-10)
    - A, 1930 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - B-L, 1930 (Box 46, Folder 1-11)
    - M-Z, 1930 (Box 47, Folder 1-11)
    - A-B, 1931 (Box 47, Folder 12-14)
    - C-N, 1931 (Box 48, Folder 1-14)
    - O-Z, 1931 (Box 49, Folder 1-10)
    - A-B, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 11-14)
    - C-R, 1932 (Box 50, Folder 1-14)
    - S-Z, 1932 (Box 51, Folder 1-5)
    - A-D, 1933 (Box 51, Folder 6-12)
    - E-Z, 1933 (Box 52, Folder 1-17)
    - A-B, 1934-1935 (Box 52, Folder 18-20)
    - C-O, 1934 (Box 53, Folder 1-15)
    - P-Z, 1934 (Box 54, Folder 1-10)
    - A-B, 1935 (Box 54, Folder 11-14)
    - B-J, 1935 (Box 55, Folder 1-12)
    - K-T, 1935 (Box 56, Folder 1-11)
    - U-Z, 1935 (Box 57, Folder 1-3)
    - A-D, 1936 (Box 57, Folder 4-10)
    - E-M, 1936 (Box 58, Folder 1-12)
    - N-Z, 1936 (Box 59, Folder 1-11)
    - A, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 12-13)
    - B-F, 1937 (Box 60, Folder 1-10)
    - G-P, 1937 (Box 61, Folder 1-12)
    - P-Z, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 1-9)
    - A, 1938 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - A-L, 1938 (Box 63, Folder 1-14)
    - M-Z, 1938 (Box 64, Folder 1-12)
    - A-E, 1939 (Box 65, Folder 1-12)
    - F-M, 1939 (Box 66, Folder 1-13)
    - N-V, 1939 (Box 67, Folder 1-13)
    - W-Z, 1939 (Box 68, Folder 1-2)
    - A-D, 1939-1940 (Box 68, Folder 3-10)
    - E-M, 1940 (Box 69, Folder 1-12)
    - N-Z, 1940 (Box 70, Folder 1-11)
    - A, 1941 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - B-E, 1941 (Box 71, Folder 1-8)
    - F-R, 1941 (Box 72, Folder 1-14)
    - S-Z, 1941 (Box 73, Folder 1-5)
    - A-E, 1940-1942 (Box 73, Folder 6-12)
    - F-P, 1942 (Box 74, Folder 1-10)
    - S-Z, 1942 (Box 75, Folder 1-5)
    - Cooperative Extension, 1942 (Box 75, Folder 6-7)
    - A-L, 1943 (Box 75, Folder 8-19)
    - M-Z, 1943 (Box 76, Folder 1-11)
    - Birds on the Home Front, 1943 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Cooperative Extension, 1943 (Box 76, Folder 13-14)
    - A-H, 1944 (Box 77, Folder 1-16)
    - H-S, 1944 (Box 78, Folder 1-16)
    - S-Z, 1944 (Box 79, Folder 1-6)
    - A-F, 1945 (Box 79, Folder 7-17)
    - G-P, 1945 (Box 80, Folder 1-17)
    - P-Z, 1945 (Box 81, Folder 1-9)
    - A-E, 1946 (Box 81, Folder 10-16)
    - F-Z, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 1-17)
    - A-I, 1947 (Box 83, Folder 1-16)
    - J-Z, 1947 (Box 84, Folder 1-16)
    - A, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - B-M, 1947-1948 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - M-Z, 1948 (Box 86, Folder 1-12)
    - A-C, 1949 (Box 86, Folder 13-19)
    - D-W, 1949 (Box 87, Folder 1-23)
    - W-Z, 1949 (Box 88, Folder 1-2)
    - A-M, 1948-1950 (Box 88, Folder 3-23)
    - N-Z, [1945-1949],1950 (Box 89, Folder 1-11)
    - A-C, 1949-1951 (Box 89, Folder 12-20)
    - D-M, 1950-1951 (Box 90, Folder 1-11)
    - N-U, [1945-1950] 1951 (Box 90, Folder 12-25)
    - W, 1948-1950, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 1-2)
    - X-Z, 1951 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - A-H, 1951-1952 (Box 91, Folder 4-15)
    - I-R, 1952 (Box 91, Folder 16-24)
    - A-H, 1952-1953 (Box 92, Folder 7-22)
    - I-N, 1953 (Box 92, Folder 23-28)
    - N-Z, unknown, 1953 (Box 93, Folder 1-11)
    - A-H, 1954 (Box 93, Folder 12-18)
    - I-L, 1954 (Box 93, Folder 19-21)
    - M-Z, unknown, 1954 (Box 94, Folder 1-10)
    - A-H, 1955 (Box 94, Folder 11-20)
    - I-J, Expeditions, 1955 (Box 94, Folder 21-22)
    - K-N, 1954-1955 (Box 95, Folder 1-5)
    - O-Z, 1955 (Box 95, Folder 6-12)
    - A-F, 1956 (Box 95, Folder 13-19)
    - G-P, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 1-10)
    - R-W, 1953-1956 (Box 96, Folder 11-16)
    - A-D, 1957 (Box 96, Folder 17-20)
    - E-Z, 1954-1957 (Box 97, Folder 1-11)
    - A-Z, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 12-23)
    - A-Z, 1959 (Box 98, Folder 1-12)
    - A-H, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 13-17)
    - I-Z, 1960 (Box 99, Folder 1-6)
    - A-Z, 1961 (Box 99, Folder 7-10)
    - A-Z, 1962 (Box 99, Folder 11-14)
    - 1963 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - 1965-1968 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - undated (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Daily File
    - January 1946-May 1947 (Box 100)
    - June 1947-July 1948 (Box 101)
    - August 1948-September 1949 (Box 102)
    - October 1949-December 1950 (Box 103)
    - January 1951-August 1953 (Box 104)
  - Professional Engagements
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1919-1937 (Box 105, Folder 1-14)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1922-1928 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1928 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1929 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1930 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1931-1937 (Box 105, Folder 6-14)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1914-1931 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Extension Lectures, 1933-1940 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1934-1940 (Box 106, Folder 2-15)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1936-1938 (Box 107, Folder 1-12)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1937-1941 (Box 108, Folder 1-13)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1914-1938 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1937-1941 (Box 109, Folder 1-13)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1941-1946 (Box 110, Folder 1-15)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1944-1948 (Box 111, Folder 1-15)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1947-1951 (Box 112, Folder 1-15)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, 1950-1959 (Box 113, Folder 1-14)
    - Engagements - Tours and Lectures, undated (Box 113, Folder 15-21)
    - Southwestern Expedition, 1939 (Box 114, Folder 1-3)
    - Spring Expedition - "Mexico, etc", 1945-1946 (Box 114, Folder 4-7)
    - Lectures, Spring Expedition, Alaska, 1948 (Box 114, Folder 8-11)
    - Spring Expedition, 1949 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Audubon Society-Screen Tours, 1953-1954 (Box 114, Folder 13-15)
    - Audubon Society-Screen Tours, 1954-1958 (Box 115, Folder 1-11)
    - Enclosures, 1956 (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Lecture Tour Itineraries, 1955-1961 (Box 115, Folder 13)
      Includes some newsclippings, fliers and a sketch
  - Louis Agassiz Fuertes
    - 1913-1926 (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - 1874-1927 (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - undated (Box 116, Folder 3, 8)
    - 1927 (Box 116, Folder 4, 7)
    - 1927-1928 (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - 1927-1932 (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - 1948-1956 (Box 116, Folder 9)
      Mary Boyton
    - 1869-1870 (Box 116, Folder 10)
      Estavan Fuertes
  - Grouse
    - 1921-October 1923, 1923 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - November-December 1923, 1923 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - 1924-1925 (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - July-October 1925, 1925 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - November-December 1925, 1925 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - January-March 1926, 1926 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - April-December 1926, 1926 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - 1927 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - 1928-1929 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - January-October 1930, 1930 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - November 1930, 1930 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - April-October 1931, 1931 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - November 1931, undated, 1931 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Grouse Reports, 1920 (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Grouse Reports, 1919-1932 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Grouse Reports, 1923-1925 (Box 118, Folder 3)
      Dispharagus in New York state, disease
    - Ruffled Grouse Disease, 1925 (Box 118, Folder 4)
      Ruffled grouse - disease
    - Grouse Reports, 1925-1926 (Box 118, Folder 5)
      Gross, Alfred O.
    - Grouse Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - "Ruffled Grouse", 1926 (Box 118, Folder 7)
      New England Ruffled Grouse Investigation Committee; Gross, Alfred O
    - Grouse Reports, 1927 (Box 118, Folder 8)
      Burckmeyer, E.K.; Ruffled grouse - disease
    - Glenside Grouse, 1927-1928 (Box 118, Folder 9)
      Ruffled Grouse
    - Grouse Expenses, 1927 (Box 118, Folder 10)
      Allen Game Farm
    - Ruffled Grouse Investigation, 1927 (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Grouse Reports, 1927 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Diseases of the Ruffled Grouse, 1927 (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - Grouse Reports, 1928 (Box 118, Folder 14, 15)
      New England Ruffled Grouse Investigation Committee; Massachusetts Fish and Game Association; Ruffled Grouse courtship
    - "Recent Development in the Rearing of Ruffled Grouse", 1931 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Grouse Reports, 1932 (Box 118, Folder 17)
      Grouse experiment station; heath hen
    - Grouse Reports, 1933 (Box 118, Folder 18)
      Grouse experiment station
    - Breeding Season Behavior of Ruffled Grouse and other Birds, 1933-1934 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Further Observations on the Mating Habits of the Ruffled Grouse and other Birds, 1933-1934 (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Grouse Reports, undated (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Ten Years Experiments on the Rearing of Ruffled Grouse in Captivity, undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Grouse Reports, 1931 (Box 119, Folder 3)
      University of Minnesota, British Committee on the Grouse in Health and Disease,; Leopold, Aldo; Ball, John N.; King, Ralph T.; Green, R.T.; Wade, E.M.; Grouse - management, Grouse - disease; Michigan, Great Britain
    - Grouse Reports, 1926-1927 (Box 119, Folder 4)
      Grouse - disease
    - Some Observations on the Blood of the Ruffled Grouse, 1927 (Box 119, Folder 5)
      Burckmeyer, E.K.; Ruffled grouse
    - Grouse Reports, 1937 (Box 119, Folder 6)
      Stafseth, H.J.; Kotlan, A.; Grouse - disease
    - Properties of Game Populations, 1931 (Box 119, Folder 7)
      Leopold, Aldo; Grouse - mobility
    - Grouse Reports, 1857-1925 (Box 119, Folder 8)
      Bibliography
    - Grouse Reports, 1934 (Box 119, Folder 9)
      Grouse program
    - Grouse Reports, undated (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Grouse Reports, 1926 (Box 119, Folder 11)
      Grouse Disease
    - Grouse Reports, 1924-1925 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Grouse Reports, 1926-1931 (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Grouse Reports, 1923-1927 (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Grouse Reports, 1929-1931 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Grouse Reports, undated (Box 119, Folder 16)
      Ruffled Grouse, Coccidiosis, artificial rearing
- Series III. Journals
  - Field Notes
    - Bird Observation, March-August 1910 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Bird Observation, September 1910-July 1911 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Bird Observation, 1912 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Bird Observation, January 1915 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Ruffled Grouse, 1920-1921 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Bird Lists, 1925-1931 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Bird Photography, 1939 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Study and Expedition Journals
    - South America, July-August 1911 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Colombia, August-December 1911 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Colombia, 1911-1912 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Bogota, Colombia, 1912 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - South America, 1911 (Box 120, Folder 12)
      Notebook
    - Labrador, May-July 1928 (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Labrador, May-July 1928 (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Allen, Elsa; Hewitt, Ollie; Labrador, 1945 (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Georgia, 1947-1948 (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - Allen, Elsa; Uppsala, Sweden, Jun-50 (Box 120, Folder 17)
- Series IV. Organizations
  - "Bird-banding Notes", 1922-1929 (Box 120, Folder 18)
    United States Department of Agriculture Bureau of Biological Survey
  - "News from Bird-banders", 1926-1927 (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - "List of Species and Numbers Banded", 1922 (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - "Constitution of the Eastern Bird-banding Association", 1923 (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - "Northeastern Bird-banding Association Announcement", 1929 (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Bird-banding Notes, 1927 (Box 120, Folder 23)
  - Bulletin - Northeastern Bird-banding Association, 1925 (Box 120, Folder 24)
  - "Bird-banding: A journal of Ornithological Investigation", 1933-1964 (Box 120, Folder 25)
  - Grand Total of Birds Nesting on the Campus, 1915 (Box 120, Folder 26)
  - Checklists of Birds, 1930 (Box 120, Folder 27)
  - Bird Census and Observation, 1932-1935 (Box 120, Folder 28)
  - Birds in Art, 1924 (Box 120, Folder 29)
  - American Ornithologists Union (AOU) "By-laws and Rules", 1915 (Box 120, Folder 30)
  - American Ornithologists Union (AOU), 1924 (Box 120, Folder 31)
  - Auk - Newsletter of the AOU, 1943-1944 (Box 120, Folder 32)
  - American Ornithologists Union (AOU) Meeting, 1938 (Box 120, Folder 33)
  - Permits and Licenses, 1917-1940 (Box 120, Folder 34)
    Bird collection
  - Permits, 1922-1935 (Box 120, Folder 35)
  - American Game Conference, 1918-1934 (Box 120, Folder 36)
  - American Ornithologists Union (AOU), 1919-1928 (Box 120, Folder 37)
  - American Association of Mammalogists, 1919-1928 (Box 120, Folder 38)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1932-1934 (Box 120, Folder 39)
  - Gamma Alpha Association, 1908-1935 (Box 120, Folder 40)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1955-1962 (Box 120, Folder 41)
  - National Wildlife Federation, 1963-1964 (Box 120, Folder 42)
  - Savage Club of Ithaca, 1935-1938 (Box 120, Folder 43)
  - New York State fish, Game and Forest League, 1914-1931 (Box 120, Folder 44)
  - Alpha Charter of the Society of Sigma X, 1914-1935 (Box 120, Folder 45)
  - Tompkins County Fish and Game Club, 1924-1925 (Box 120, Folder 46)
  - Miscellaneous Organizations, 1916-1927 (Box 120, Folder 47)